

Bradley GyemiFull Stack + Dev-Ops Developer
Software Engineer

- ▶ Born 1997 in Windsor, Canada
- Canadian Citizen
- Fluent English Speaking

Education

09/2015 - 09/2020

Honours Computer Science (with 3 year Internship)

University of Windsor Software Eng. Specialization Capstone Thesis: Correcting Mouse Input Error With Linear Regression

Skills

Software development	6+ Years
Web security	3+ yrs.
CI/CD Build Engineer	1+ yrs.
Web development	6+ yrs.
Web 3.0 and Blockchain	2+ yrs.
Systems Administration	3+ yrs.
Mobile IOS/Android	3+ yrs

Summary

27 year old mid-level full-stack software engineer with experience as a dev-ops lead and a technical lead. Proficient as a mobile developer on IOS and Android as well as using React Native for cross platform development. Built multiple new features on Qlik's mobile App. Designed, built, and managed micro-service back end using Docker, AWS, and Node as the Tech Lead at Regulars and Co. Front end UI/UX design, implementation, and web hosting using Nextjs and Vercel for both Blue Joy Homes and JV Massage Therapy. Built the entire tech stack for advertising, scheduling, score submission, notifications, and team rankings for the London Beach Volleyball League as the sole proprietor. Teamwork, physical fitness, and stress management are strong habits learned through 2 seasons overseas as a pro athlete. Professional, integrous, experienced, and skilled.

Experience

Technical Lead

Regulars and Co.

05/2022 - Present

Responsible for managing a team of 3 developers to build the the software suite offered by Regulars and Co. This includes a mobile app for customers, web console and POS interface for merchants. High level micro-service architecture design and implementation. Agile leader and sprint manager. Responsible for high level system design and delivery.

- Front end: React Native, React, shadon, and Figma

- Back end: Expressjs, MongoDB, microservice architecture

Containers/ Images: Docker, Terraform, AWS,Pipeline: AWS CodeDeploy and Github Actions

- Testing: Jest and Codmium

Technical Lead

05/2022 - Present

Global Warranty (Contract for Regulars and Co)

Responsible for managing a team of developers to build a distributed rewards program for dealerships which sell Global Warranty car insurance. It includes a web console and multi-layer user authentication system for Global personnel. A limited web console for managers and a mobile app for salesmen was included in the package distributed to dealerships. The system allowed Global personnel to create, announce, update, track, and distribute prizes. It allowed dealership managers to manage personnel and track their sales progress. It allowed salesmen to get notifications about prizes and receive recognition for performing well

- Front end: React Native, React, shadon, and Figma

- Back end: Expressjs, MongoDB,

- Containers/ Images: Docker, Apache

- Pipeline: Github Actions

- Testing: Jest, Mocha, Chai and Codmium

Awards & Accomplishments

05/2020

Frank De-Marco Award

University of Windsor

Awarded to a University of Windsor Student who shows an outstanding level of excellence in both their academic and athletic performance.

05/2018

Karen Harvey Award

University of Windsor

Awarded to a University of Windsor Volleyball player and Windsor native who exemplifies high performance, team leadership, and sportsmanship.

Proficiency

- HTML, Javascript & Frameworks
- CSS, SASS, SCSS
- Python
- SQL & NoSQL
- PHP, C, C++
- React Native, Java, Gradle
- Docker & YAML
- Github Actions, AWS

Contact

- 637 Griffith St, London ON
- □ +1 615 393 1229
- bradgy2008@hotmail.com

Dev-ops & Software Engineer

Mobile Team Lund Sweden Qlik

Responsible for managing the mobile team's development pipelines to allow for frequent and smooth patches and product deployments. Updates to Docker images and their Github Actions workflows allowed the team make changes and push releases to iOS App Store and the Android Play Store at required business intervals. I also worked on feature development in React Native and worked with representatives from other teams in the company to build multi-product features and deploy synchronously within the company.

- Front end: React Native
- Back end: GoLang
- Containers/Images: Docker + Github Container Registry
- Pipeline: Github Actions, CircleCi, and Jenkins
- Server Systems Admin: MacOS and Ubuntu build agents running on a Jenkins system

Professional Volleyball Player | Youth Coach

10/2020 - 10/2022

Lund VK

Swedish Volleyball Eliteserien

As a professional athlete I was responsible for:

- 2 training sessions a day
- Researching opponents through analysis of game film
- Fundamental skill development of younger players
- Performing at an elite level in matches.

As a coach for the youth development program I was responsible for

- Developing local young Swedish players.
- Designing practice plans to map out athlete skill development
- Making the practices fun for the athletes to ensure that they return to training.

Web Application Developer

01/2017 - 01/2019

Windsor Hiram Walker Branch AppDev Pernod Ricard

Responsibilities included:

- Building additions and updates to various different company applications.
- Building a web-based IOS application for the company used by all employees to check into work and update their current status so that co-workers could easily locate each other and know whether they were: in a meeting, at lunch, available, etc.
- Augmenting existing apps with IOS and Android push notifications using Firebase, Xcode, and a notification service called OneSignal.
- Debugging issues with apps which senior developers failed to solve quickly.
- Designing efficient and comprehensive unit tests for solo projects and existing ones.
- Sufficiently documenting all changes along with consistent collaboration with team members regarding best practices.

These projects required use of Java, JWT, Javascript frameworks like Sencha Architect, HTML, CSS, XCode, Firebase, Apache server, Git and Atlassian, and Bitbucket. They were run through a development pipeline called Jenkins.